fitlife.tv 2018-12-28

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for **www.FitLife.TV**

This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this Web site. It will notify you of the following:

1\. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the Web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.

2\. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.

3\. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.

4\. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via e-mail or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via e-mail in the future to tell you about our specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy. We will not share and or give out your private information and email. **We are a spam-free site.**

**Your Access To and Control Over Information**

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time.

**You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the e-mail address or phone number given on our Web site:**

· See what data we have about you, if any.

· Change/correct any data we have about you.

· Have us delete any data we have about you.

· Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

**Security**

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the Web site, your information is protected both online and offline. Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way.

You can verify this by looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the Web page. While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline.

Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

What Our Clients Say*

Glenn was in an accident with a hockey puck that made it so his mouth had to be wired shut! While he was going through recovery he found that Organifi Protein sustained him in a healthy way where he was able to maintain his muscle mass while still be able to loose weight. 

**-Tragedy Turns to Opportunity, Weightloss and Holistic Health**

Glenn was in an accident with a hockey puck that made it so his mouth had to be wired shut! While he was going through recovery he found that Organifi Protein sustained him in a healthy way where he was able to maintain his muscle mass while still be able to loose weight. 

**-Tragedy Turns to Opportunity, Weightloss and Holistic Health**

*Results may vary by individual
